AIRONAS BILEVICIUS

ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING

CONTACT

970-887-2922

aironas@colostate.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/aironasbilevicius
3354 Liverpool

Fort Collins, CO 80526

SKILLS

GitHub, Cadence, MATLAB, Java, Waveforms, Systems Analysis, Signal Analysis, Circuit Design, Project Engineering

Teamwork, Organization, Technical Writing, Bilingual (Lithuanian), Responsibility

EDUCATION

Electrical Engineering

Colorado State University

2021-2024

Current Cumulative GPA: 3.425 Relative Coursework:

- ECE 461 Power Systems
- ECE 565 Electrical Power Engineering
- ECE 401 Senior Design
- ATS 550 Atmospheric Radiation and Remote Sensing
- ECE 251 Introduction to Microcontrollers and IoT

Senior Design Project

RamBOTs

- This is an Outreach project from CSU that works with electrical, computer, and mechanical engineers to make younger generations interested in engineering.
- The main project is a robot dog/ram.
- The groups goal for the project were to make it play fetch, start up on the first try, and walk at games.
- I will be focusing on the power systems of the project.

Transfer

Red Rocks Community College

2019-2021

PROFILE

I am a fourth-year Electrical Engineering student at Colorado State University. I started schooling at Red Rocks Community College, studied through the pandemic, and was able to transfer while adapting to the situations that were presented to me. I have some experience working with a CO-OP, and power systems, but I am willing to learn other fields that electrical engineering has to offer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Intern

Poudre Valley REA

June 2023 - August 2023

- Worked with a team to help improve the GIS Mapping of the area that PVREA services.
- Went to the field with the field engineers to look at projects, staking, and how to communicate with clients.
- Learned how to use Excel, Teams, and outlook in different ways.
- Observed and helped a coworker fix and test regulators, reclosers, and transformers.
- Explored the NCIS software that is used for GIS, and CIS services.
- Gained an understanding of the different slang and terminology commonly used by coworkers and clients.

Electrician

AKT Electrics

June 2022 - January 2023

- Tested installed devices to check if there were any errors.
- Installed various devices like receptacles, pendants, undercabinet lights, and chandeliers.
- Bent and assembled PVC for underground wire connections.
- Ran home runs and connection wire for the rough-in process.
- Wired a panel so a new job site would have power.
- Organized materials so the crew would be able to find materials quicker.
- Worked with a team to help increase efficiency and teaching opportunities.

Maintenance

Condominium Management Company May 2021 - August 2021 and Winter 2020 - 2021

- Worked with others to safely take apart decks and repair them.
- Painted buildings to help increase the aesthetics of the condos.
- Shoveled snow to allow people to leave their condominiums.
- Maintained grounds by mowing the grass, applying fertilizer, and repairing sprinklers.
- Worked in groups to delegate tasks and get work done.

Laborer

Big Valley Construction

May 2020 - August 2020

- Operated heavy equipment such as a forklift and bobcat.
- Assisted project managers with repairs.
- Helped maintain a clean job site.